[upbeat music playing]
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ Out of the blue ♪
♪ You changed your mind ♪
♪ Nothing's real ♪
♪ I didn't change mine ♪
♪ We used to dance... ♪
Hi!
♪  We used to laugh... ♪
I'm gonna take this.
♪  You swore we never stopped dancing ♪
♪ You felt all the same feelings ♪
Good deal.
Thank you for picking me up.
♪ Way ♪
[phone ringing]
Hi.
How's it going? How was your flight?
Long, of course. You know?
How are you? What's going on?
Uh, not much.
Just got back from practice. Um...
Not much else.
What are you up to the rest of the day?
-I'm going to head into the office.
-[Nick] Nice.
Well, I miss you,
and I hope that we can see each other,
sooner than later and not go too long.
Yeah, well, once we figure it out,
once the season's over,
probably my first stop will be LA.
I love you
and have a good game,
and I'll talk to you soon, okay?
-Talk to you. I love you. Bye.
-Okay, I love you. Bye.
[Heather] The upside about being
a real estate agent is the flexible hours.
I've been gone for about a week,
I was visiting my hot man.
He plays professional hockey in Slovakia.
He's working basically full-time,
so I'm kinda the one who has to leave,
go see him, and make that work.
It's hard because if you don't work
and hustle, you don't get paid.
♪ Ready or not ♪
♪ Here I come ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Feel my power, power ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Hey ♪
This is that house that looks like
an eighties porn star built it.
[Brett] So why are we looking at it?
-[woman] It's just a silly really house.
-[Brett] It's your dream house?
-No, I was telling--
-You'll put it on your vision board?
I had a vision board for my relationship
and it worked.
-Aw!
-[Brett] Okay.
-[woman] That's so cute.
-[Maya] I know.
Hey!
Hey, girl!
[Maya] So are you excited to be back?
She's so excited she forgot
her computer to work.
[chuckles]
I just came to see you girls.
I'm not working today. [chuckles]
I just got back, girl.
-[Maya] How was it?
-[Heather] It was good.
I mean, I got to be with my love.
I'm sorry. What is he?
-He's a hockey player.
-Oh, got it. Oh, cool!
And he's sexy and beautiful,
so that helps.
My boyfriend is seven years
younger than me.
He got asked to go play with the KHL,
which is the Kontinental Hockey League.
He was living out in California.
That's when we met.
He was playing for a team here.
I think a lot of men think
that I'm, like, their little Barbie doll.
You know, I have to be a certain way,
act a certain way,
and he's the first guy
that's ever, like, really let me myself.
When I'm with him, it's amazing.
[Chrishell] But aren't a lot of them,
like, they have to put in teeth, right?
[Heather] Yeah, he lost, like,
half of his two front teeth.
-Yeah, but I think it's sexy.
-Eek.
Did you just say he lost two of his teeth
and you think it's sexy?
Oh, I think it's so hot
when a man looks like that.
Yeah. Do you want a hockey man, girl?
They had to have all of their teeth.
That's my only criteria.
[Christine] Heather's been working at
the Oppenheim Group for almost four years.
She started right before I did.
I don't like Heather as a person,
and I get annoyed by Heather all the time.
It's just because of the way she looks,
because of the way she dresses,
because of the way she speaks,
it's because of the lack of wheels
turning up there.
-Is he moving here or are you--
-He's not gonna move here.
He can't, 'cause he has to train.
I mean, he did really well over there,
so I know they're gonna want him back
and offer him something.
It's heartbreaking.
-You got to drink.
-I know, I need a cocktail.
[Mary] We should get drinks.
My birthday's coming up.
Oh, wait! That's right! That's right.
Okay, when's your birthday?
-The 29th.
-Mine's the 21st.
We should do, like,
a joint birthday party or something.
That'd be awesome. Oh, yeah!
-That would be fun. That would be fun.
-Yeah.
What's up with you? How's the hubby?
I'm tired between flying and working.
And, you know,
it's a little bit challenging,
because I'm spending my time
between Miami and LA,
you know, trying to do stuff there,
and obviously have clients here.
But it's good. Like, he comes
to see me when he can.
He's super busy with work,
but I'm happy.
Like, it's good. Yeah.
My situation is similar to Heather's.
We are doing long distance
with the guys we love.
With her, it's a little bit different.
She cannot just go on a weekend
to see him.
It's 13 hours of flights.
[Christine] Heather,
get on your computer and do some work!
[scoffs] I don't have it, girl.
-Can I borrow yours?
-No, 'cause you might not give it back.
Of course I would give your computer back.
[dogs barking]
-[Chrishell] The bitches are fighting.
-[Maya] Which ones?
[chuckles]
♪ Hold up
I'm just getting started ♪
♪ When I have to roll up
You know it's a party ♪
♪ Let my hair down
Having some fun ♪
♪ Hands up
Marching to the beat of my drum ♪
♪ They're my ladies
Around the globe ♪
♪ Live it up
Live it up ♪
♪ All my ladies from the show ♪
♪ Making moves and we just don't stop ♪
♪ My ladies around the globe ♪
♪Work it, love it, live it up ♪
-So sorry I'm running a little late.
-No problem at all.
-How are you?
-I'm good, thank you.
-Thank you for seeing me.
-Of course!
-This house, I'm so excited to show you.
-Yes!
-[Mary] Close to everything.
-[woman] Oh, wow!
-Yes. It's huge!
-[Mary] This is why I wanted to bring you.
[chuckles]
I would never think
that this house could be this big.
Yeah, so this is about
just under 5,000 square feet.
It's kind of what I think
you're looking for.
[Mary] I love the LA real estate market
because I'm competitive.
I wanna win. I wanna get
my clients their home,
I wanna get the highest price
for my sellers, beating out other buyers,
making sure your client is the one
that gets their offer accepted.
It's exhilarating.
You mentioned you like contemporary,
high ceilings, natural light,
and this one is really spectacular.
I think, they really did a good job,
of making
a very nice contemporary modern feel,
but also they have elements
in here, that bring in the warmth.
-[woman] Yes, like the wood...
-[Mary] So it's not too cold.
It's definitely my style.
These are all pocket doors,
so you can open up
this set of doors and this set of doors,
and you really get
the whole indoor-outdoor living.
You get all the natural light
and the breeze that comes in.
[woman] I really like that.
-This reminds me of Turkey. Back home.
-Oh, really.
Whoever built this house
must be from Turkey.
[Mary chuckles] All the olive trees.
[woman] Yeah. Exactly.
See, it's meant to be.
This is such a perfect house for you.
So, master bedroom.
[woman] Big.
-[Mary] Yes. [chuckles]
-[woman] Beautiful!
Yes. So you got your own private balcony
off the master suite.
You told me that every room
has a balcony, right?
Exactly. Every room has an en suite bath
and its own private balcony.
So the shower,
see the size of the shower here?
It's amazing. Dual shower heads.
You got this beautiful tub.
[woman] Super nice.
[Mary] And also we have
a little living area up here as well.
-[woman] Wow.
-[Mary] What do you think?
It definitely has all the elements that,
you know, we discussed on the phone.
-I'm 30 now and I need to slow down.
-Okay.
This will be the home
and hopefully a family inside of it.
That's the main reason I want to be here,
and also trying to convince my man
-to maybe have a family one day.
-[chuckles]
I'll-- I'll handle this part of that.
I'm glad you love it. I thought, that
this would be right kind of up your alley,
of what you said you were looking for.
Perfect.
-Now I feel more hopeful, you know?
-[chuckles]
It feels so far away
when you're over there.
-I think I might take it.
-Really?
'Cause I know you're looking
for a house, too. You were telling me.
Romain and I are-- are really thinking
of trying to buy a place,
so I'm absolutely in love
with this home, too,
so if you don't get it, I might.
[chuckles]
♪ Hold on
I just got to let you know ♪
-I love you.
♪ Higher and I can't get enough ♪
♪ I want reach out and touch it ♪
Perfect, thank you.
Thank you.
This place is beautiful.
-Nice and romantic for our anniversary.
-Yeah.
-One year already.
-I know.
I'm glad you ate the hat on me.
[chuckles] What?
Romain has a very good vocabulary.
You just can't understand,
what he says a lot of the time,
because he just has a very thick accent.
I think he's doing very well.
Better than me with French, anyway.
You hit hard on me.
-What?
-Our first date.
I know certain words like santé.
Bottoms up, like cheers.
Of course, I'm the one who knows that one.
I hit hard on you?
Yeah. [chuckles]
-You hit on me.
-Yeah, maybe.
You reached over and grabbed my hand,
and I was like, "Hell, yeah."
And then you kissed me.
It was meant to be.
It was all you.
[Romain laughs]
-Hi.
-Hi. How are you?
May I get you something to drink?
Do you have espresso martinis?
-Espresso martini?
-[Mary] Yeah, please.
And would you like to order?
No, I'm just gonna do a margarita.
I don't know how to say it,
but the pappardelle with the wild boar.
Nastria cinghiale.
So much more beautiful when you say it.
Bene, then the nastria
and the pizza margharita. Grazie.
-Thank you.
-Prego. Salute.
I've been married twice before.
The first husband has passed away,
and the second husband,
it just didn't work out.
It wasn't the right relationship to be in.
Never thought I wanted
to get married again.
How's your work going?
So the boys took us up to see this house.
It's one
of the most amazing properties I've seen.
[Jason] It's over 4,000 square feet,
this rooftop deck.
The largest rooftop deck
of any property ever listed in the hills.
You have to come see it.
It's 40 million dollars.
It is one of the most epic homes
in the hills right now.
I'm thinking about
which buyer I'm gonna get.
That's gonna be a war
between you guys to find a buyer, right?
Oh, I'm winning.
[laughs]
For sure.
-Espresso martini.
-Thank you. Oh, it looks good.
Prego.
-Salute.
-[Romain] Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Cheers, my love. Happy anniversary.
Happy anniversary.
I don't know if I'm ready to turn 38.
-I feel old.
-Why?
'Cause I'm 38.
-Yeah, but...
-[chuckles]
I just feel like it's a number.
I mean--
Yeah, it's more about how you feel.
So, babe, you're 25, you're not really
that much older than my son.
[Mary] I have a son. He's 21.
I did have him when I was very young.
I was 16.
I've been a single mom ever since.
I don't see him ever stepping in,
like a father figure,
and Austin doesn't need that,
but they get along great.
Do you feel like you're missing out?
A little bit.
I just, like, you know, I don't...
We should probably talk about this,
if we are thinking of a future together.
Then...
-Do you want kids?
-I just feel like, you know...
I don't know. I'm saying that...
I didn't plan to have kids,
you know, right now.
I definitely want kids.
How many?
I don't know. One or two.
Like, in an ideal world,
how-- how soon would you have them?
Between 30 and 35,
which is in five or ten years.
Because of our age difference,
that might be a problem.
Because I've got...
-a couple years left.
-I know. I mean, the thing is--
And you might not want them
for a couple years.
I've been there. I've done that.
I would only consider having another child,
if it's someone I absolutely love,
and it's very very important to them.
So what would happen,
if you're not ready for a couple years,
and then it's too late?
I don't know.
♪ Try not to let the burn ♪
♪ Become a scar ♪
♪ Goodbye ♪
[Maya] What are you wearing
to Mary's birthday party?
[Chrishell] I'm not sure yet.
[dogs barking]
[woman] How was your open house?
[Chrishell] Amazing. So good.
Put so many offers in.
[Maya] I feel like with open houses,
like I literally picked up one buyer
from an open house, and I probably sent,
probably three hundred of them.
[Christine]
I've had so many, like, prospects
where I'm like, "Yeah, this is
going somewhere!" and then they ghost.
I'm like, if I wanted someone to ghost,
I'd be on Tinder.
[engine revs]
All right, a guy with a small dick,
we got you.
[Christine] What the heck?
It's like so show-offy, I can't stand it.
It bugs me.
-[Chrishell] Hi.
-[Christine] Hey.
-Hey, girl.
-Hey. You look pretty.
Thank you.
Oh, how was your--
You had your dinner last night.
Happy anniversary.
Sorry, I forgot to text you.
It was not what I expected at all.
It was kind of awful. [scoffs]
-What happened?
-It was awful?
The date started great, like,
beautiful place, we were getting along,
and we started talking about what we want
to do, moving forward as a couple,
and as we started talking about it,
his age obviously
has a role to play in it.
So I asked him if he feels like
he's missing out on anything,
and he was like, "Yeah, sometimes."
What do you mean, "sometimes"?
Yeah, I mean, what is he missing out on?
He just turned 25.
He can rent a car now. He's living life.
What is he missing out on?
I'm so confused.
Then it gets worse. It gets way worse.
He doesn't want kids for ten years.
-What?
-Ten years?
Ten years, so if he does, what does
that do? Like, I'm gonna be 48.
-But you could, like, freeze your eggs--
-At 48?
No, now. Right now.
Yeah, but having a kid at 48?
When he's ready?
You could do a surrogate.
Just plop him in someone else.
I mean, I'm just saying.
Oh, my god. I'm like, shaking. I just...
I thought we were so good.
-It's gonna be okay.
-[Chrishell] No, don't cry. Don't cry.
Are you crying?
No, don't cry, Mary. Oh.
No more sad.
[muffled speech]
[Maya] It's gonna be fine. Don't cry.
Give him time.
[Christine] Mary does fall
fast and hard in love.
I want to make sure
that Romain's looking out for Mary.
Are you looking to get married,
like, is that your goal?
I-- I never thought that I wanted--
-I needed to get married again...
-Yeah.
...um, but with him, I would-- I want to.
And I thought that's where it was going.
-So...
-[Chrishell] I'm sorry.
♪ We could cry
We could cry for yesterdays ♪
♪ I won't give
I won't give, ooh ♪
♪ I was born for this ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ Na, na, na, na, na
Na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na... ♪
[Heather]
This listing is a huge listing for me,
and if I get it sold, it will really show
Jason and Brett and the office,
that I'm serious, because traveling
back and forth to see Nick,
you know, sometimes my mind
and my heart is not here in LA.
And I was the top selling girl for a while,
and I wanna get back to that place.
Hi.
-Hi! How are you?
-I'm good, how are you?
-Good. I'm Catherine.
-Heather. Nice to meet you.
-Thanks so much for coming.
-My pleasure.
So they just finished the renovations.
I'm super excited to get this staged...
-It's beautiful.
-...and get started. Yes.
Staging a home is bringing in furniture,
and working with a staging company,
to basically make an environment,
where a client will envision themselves,
living in the home. And it's fun.
It's fun to be creative.
Who doesn't like decorating
and pulling everything together?
I want the vibe to be for, like, a couple,
um, more of an entertainment home,
-not so much family vibe.
-Okay.
So that was my question:
when you think about this house,
it's not for young children
or school-aged children--
No, 'cause we're off Sunset, so it's
more of like a lifestyle-entertainment,
so I want the vibe
to definitely reflect that.
-Yeah, I wanna really feature the kitchen.
-Okay.
It's such a beautiful kitchen.
They put a lot of work into it.
The island is Calcutta gold marble.
Each slab was 10,000.
I think total, it was like 40,000
for the counters.
And the cabinets are
reclaimed wood veneer.
So I wanna do something simple in here,
but make it livable
and beautiful and tasteful.
So what would you do in here?
Well, I think the reclaimed wood veneer
gives it sort of a rustic feel.
You know, it's definitely not
shiny and slick,
which I think is a really nice offset
with the polished marble.
-Maybe some leather stools for sure.
-I like that.
This will be a fun stage.
Yeah, I'm excited.
And I'm thinking all the colors will just
be, you know, white, really neutrals
-for the most part.
-Okay.
That, like, California modern,
casual, chic... Yeah.
-Beautiful.
-I think it will be really pretty.
I'm just kinda gonna lean into the fact
that there's a rustic vibe.
I'm so sorry.
I have to take this call real quick.
-That's fine.
-Give me a sec? Yeah? Okay.
[Christine] Hi, babe.
Babe?
-Hi.
-[Nick] Yo.
What's up?
So I got some news today, actually.
That scares me. What?
I talked to my agent
before I got on the phone with you,
and we have agreed to sign
with a team in Sweden,
for next year and the year after,
so it's a two-year deal in Sweden.
This was the best one that we had,
so I kind of just agreed today.
Wait babe, just take me off FaceTime,
so we can talk about this,
'cause we have a lot to discuss right now,
so take me off.
So what are you talking about? Two years?
That's such a long time, like...
[Heather] Long distance sucks.
I was really hoping that he would sign
in the US this coming year.
It would make it easier for me.
One, to see him. Two, to have a career,
and not have to make a huge decision
about what I'm gonna do.
I can't do it right now, I can't talk.
I'm at work so we're gonna have
to talk later, okay?
♪ I know what it's like... ♪
I know.
Okay, I love you.
Bye.
♪ Knowing nothing
But the beat of your own heart ♪
♪ And if I start to fall too fast ♪
♪ I breathe ♪
[Heather] Sorry, where were we?
[Catherine] I think I'm gonna do
white linen upholstery.
-Okay.
-Match the dining room chairs.
♪ Take a breath
Let it go ♪
♪ There's a spark inside ♪
♪ I can feel it ♪
♪ Let it rise
Let it rise ♪
♪ And now the world is calling ♪
♪ Underneath the brighter sky ♪
♪ Anything can happen now ♪
♪ Anything can happen ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I feel alive, feel alive, feel alive ♪
♪ For the very first time ♪
-Happy birthday!
-Thanks! Happy birthday to you!
Happy belated birthday.
-Yes.
-Aw, thank you!
Of course.
Hi, how are you?
-Happy birthday! You look beautiful.
-Thank you.
-You look so pretty. Love it.
-We were saying how beautiful you look.
-Happy birthday!
-I love these dresses.
-Hi, honey.
-How are you?
-How are you? You look so pretty.
You look like a supermodel.
-You do too. Good to see you.
-Thank you!
♪ I'm feeling good, yeah... ♪
Party's official!
[Heather] Cheers, babe. Happy birthday.
You look so beautiful, how are you?
Where's Justin?
-He's filming.
-Aw.
He says happy birthday.
-Aw, thank you. Happy birthday!
-This is so pretty. Aw, this is sweet.
-Hey!
-What's up, man? Hi, sweetheart.
-You look great.
-Birthday girl.
-Hi.
Okay. Perfect.
So I wanna make a toast--
Wait, wait, I haven't done my shot yet.
We're cheersing to Mary and Chrishell.
Mary has been, like,
a lifelong friend of mine.
We've, like, you're my ride-or-die bitch.
You know that.
We've been through hell and back together
and I love you so much,
and I seriously feel like
you're my sister.
And Chrishell, I don't know you that well,
but I'm going to know you well,
so as Britney Spears would say,
"You better work, bitch."
Keep up. Cheers to that!
Whoo!
-Cheers.
-Agh.
-It's burning my chest.
I'm sorry. Do you have a napkin?
Is it-- [chuckles] No.
Oh, gross.
Hi, honey, how are you?
You're young like my man, huh?
[giggles] You guys are both cougars. Rawr.
How long have you guys
even been dating?
-Over a year now.
-Over a year?
Yeah, a bit over a year.
-Twenty-five, right?
-Yes.
Are you an old soul or a young soul?
-I feel like an old one.
-Oh.
-I mean, I know what I want.
-Yeah.
You do? Good for you!
[Chrishell]
Does he really know what he wants at 25?
Hopefully, we'll see,
but... I don't know. [chuckles]
Am I allowed to ask what is that?
No, I won't ask.
-Yeah, I wanna hear this. What is that?
-Yeah, why not? What do you want?
Are you guys getting married?
Know what, I thought about it.
Nice to meet you. Hi.
-So where's your husband?
-Miami.
Is he gonna come see you?
Yeah, he couldn't come,
so it sucks you know?
-It's so hard, I know. Trust me, I know.
-It's hard.
It's sad, it's like--
I'm gonna fly next week for two days
and come back here.
Yeah, I wish it was that easy
for me to go to Slovakia.
-Have you talked to Nick?
-He texts me early in the morning.
I mean we're like such, like, different,
opposite sides of the world right now.
-Yeah.
-He's like nine hours ahead, so...
-No, we're talking about, uh--
-My boyfriend.
You know, he's overseas,
it's just the time difference with the--
-[Brett] What's going on with that?
-[laughs] Nothing is going on with that.
Everything's fine.
Don't give her shade.
You don't know my relationship.
I agree with that.
I don't need your approval
of my boyfriend.
You don't need our approval,
but we have to meet him.
Of course you're gonna meet him.
You guys are my family,
-but I also don't need anyone's approval.
-That's all I'm asking.
Okay, that's fair enough,
but I don't care what you say. I love him.
-So it's my decision.
-You do care what I say, but okay.
Listen, Brett wants Heather to stay in LA
just because, he wants her
to make money for the brokerage.
I don't know why, though.
She's basic, but whatever.
-Wait, what are we talking about?
-Yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I don't like him trying to--
I mean he doesn't know him.
He is the last person
to give relationship--
He has no... He's not married,
never dated,
-like, I don't need relationship--
-It is what it is.
Don't take it personal.
That's why, like, listen,
I'm gonna have your back on that,
because it's like, listen,
that's not fair for you
to micro-analyze your situation.
That's not fair, Brett. I don't think so.
I don't like you, but I don't have to be
your friend to, like, see what's going on
-and realize that's not fair.
-You're not my friend?
-I mean, not yet, bitch, but--
-What?!
Excuse me?
I did nothing to you.
I went through dinner
we had at a restaurant, um...
I was just shocked and hurt, to be honest.
Like, when I thought that you were saying,
"Oh, it's okay for now, like whatever."
I thought that that was...
You were on the same page as me.
I think this scared me...
because I'm so in,
like, this relationship
and I want so much out of it,
and I am one year older
and closer to 40.
Can you handle that?
-Yeah, you're scared, right? [chuckles]
-Yeah.
Really scared.
I like being scared.
-♪ Happy birthday to you... ♪
-Mary, Chrishell, get up here.
♪ Happy birthday
Dear Mary and Chrishell ♪
You kind of caught me off guard,
when you said you're not my friend.
Like, what did I do to you?
There was a client.
I was helping him look
for a house in the Hills,
and he made it seem like you were
maybe approaching him as well.
Okay, but did I know him first?
No, you didn't know him first.
But how do you know that?
What if he's lying to you?
He's not lying to me.
I have been working with him for months,
and you came back,
you had a conversation with him,
and that's when it got brought up, that you
worked at the same brokerage that I did.
Oh, God. Ah!
[cheering]
My first reaction was, you know,
how unprofessional,
-how disrespectful, you know--
-Mm-hmm.
Business is business. Money is money.
That's and important thing.
I know that.
I'm saying maybe he's the problem.
Why would he approach me and tell me
that you approached him?
Maybe he wanted to work with me
without stepping on your toes...
[Christine] It just doesn't make sense.
You know how men are.
What if your client was lying?
He's not lying.
But then why was he talking to me then?
-Heather, please.
-People lie.
I just feel like you need to respect,
what's yours is yours,
and what's mine is mine.
♪ This town, this town
Gonna beat you down ♪
♪ Are you gonna let it? ♪
-Hey, girl.
-Hey, how are you?
Sorry for being late. Traffic.
-Oh, no. It's okay.
-You know how it is.
-Thank you so much for meeting me.
-Of course!
Just wanted to kind of like sit down
with you one-on-one,
and ask you a couple questions
just because, like,
you guys have all
known each other so long.
Seriously, it's like high school right?
And we're too old for that shit.
[chuckles] I know.
So it's like a fine balance.
-Yeah.
-Sometimes...
I just feel like Christine
goes a little too far.
Yeah. She has no filter.
Like, whatever she thinks she just says.
Well, I was one of the first girls
who joined the office.
Mary and Christine used to be roommates,
and they were kind of like one unit,
so I didn't feel like she was trying
to make too much effort
-to, you know, become friends with me.
-Yeah.
Uh, but it took time.
Probably two years.
-Two years?
-Yeah.
-Oh, my God.
-I know.
-But I feel like now she's--
-I have a long road ahead of me.
-I know. [chuckles]
-Are you feeling okay after last night?
I'm feeling good.
I mean, actually, I didn't really drink.
How did you get out of that?
I had water.
-Oh, my God, I should've done that.
-I know.
-You dumped it out and put water in it?
-Okay.
I was trying to say no,
and I don't think Christine
was having any of that.
-Christine was pushing you hard for that.
-So I'm paying for it today.
I know. I mean, I wanted to drink,
but I think I might be pregnant.
Oh, my God!
-Yeah.
-When do you know?
Well, I'm late, and...
Oh, my god, that's so exciting!
You guys had been trying
for a while, right?
We've been trying. I mean,
the thing is I had two miscarriages.
So nobody really knows,
but I'm just trying to keep it on the low
until, uh, I figure out if it's safe,
but it's very, very early.
-I will send you all the positive...
-Thank you.
-...good vibes, keep my fingers crossed.
-Please, please, please.
-Yes, of course.
-So, we'll see.
♪ Come to life ♪
-[knock on door]
-Hi, babe.
You live in Hollywood. You shouldn't
leave your door open like that.
[laughs] Hey, how are you?
-How are you, Princess Layla?
-Good. Thanks.
-How was your day?
-[Mary] It was good.
Um, this might... [chuckles]
I need to clean off the lip of this thing.
It's like the dishwasher.
I see lipstick on those glasses already.
I feel like I'm in a Cheesecake Factory.
No, it's from the--
It's from the dishwasher, I promise.
[chuckles]
I mean, that's why you're supposed
to hand wash wine glasses,
but I'm lazy and I don't.
You wanna sit down?
Yeah, let's take a seat.
Come on, Zelly.
All right, so here, come here.
Show me this side.
What's going on with this?
-I just was feeling very harajuku.
-This is crazy.
-Wish I had chopsticks.
-Hara what?
Harajuku. Harajuku Girls.
-It's cute. It's you. It's fitting.
-Thanks.
Hi, Zelda. Come sit down.
So tell me about the other night.
Like, at the party.
I thought we were having
a really good time, and, um...
I got some tension from Heather.
We're fighting with each other.
We were talking about
a client, that had approached me, and told
me, that Heather was trying to poach him.
And I told her, I said,
"That's really unprofessional,
and I think poorly of you for doing that."
It's like real estate 101.
I think it really hurt her feelings,
that I said that.
But you were just like kind of...
You were on one.
You and your, like, little devil horns.
Honestly, I'm tired
of filtering myself and apologizing.
I'm just like-- I don't even know
how to describe this. I'm just like...
Oh, don't wanna offend this person.
Oh, don't wanna--
It's like I'm a news anchor.
It's like what the fuck?
I didn't sign up for this.
I gotta be so careful about
what I say around people?
It's like Jesus, you know?
It's just like--
I just want to say, whatever the fuck
I want, and no one to get offended.
Is that so much to ask?
We're a badass crew to hang out with,
you know?
-It, like, takes a special type.
-Yeah, you have to have thick skin.
Bottom line, you're a professional.
Act like a professional.
You have to prove, that you're serious
about your job, like the rest of us.
By showing that you don't have a backbone,
you're just wishing and hoping
it will go away. Doesn't work like that.
I just don't respect her.
♪ Nothing's gonna slow me down ♪
♪ There's a beautiful day ♪
♪ Headed your way ♪
♪ Keep your head up, up, up
You'll be okay ♪
♪ A beautiful day ♪
♪ Waiting for you ♪
♪ Just open your eyes ♪
♪ You'll see it's true ♪
♪ There's a beautiful day ♪
♪ Headed your way ♪
♪ Keep your head up, up, up ♪
♪ You'll be okay ♪
♪ A beautiful day ♪